scoutlander.com 2011-06-09

# ScoutLander Privacy Statement

At ScoutLander, we respect and protect the privacy or our customers and those who use our websites. The following Privacy Statement provides details about how your personal information is collected and used. This privacy statement applies to the network of Wysitech websites, products and services that are located in, but not limited to the Wysitech.com, ScoutLander.com domains. 

**Information Collection and Use  
** ScoutLander is the sole owner of information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. ScoutLander collects information from our users at several different points on our website and sign up process.   
We required customers who register to use the services offered on our site (collectively, the “Service”) to give us contact information, such as their name, address, phone number, and e-mail address.   
Users can update or remove their personal information at any time by logging into the Website and editing their Personal Information within “My Profile”. Customers can view their updated profile to confirm their edits have been made. 

**Sharing and Usage  
** We will never share, sell, or rent your personal information with third parties for their promotional use. We may disclose or report personal information in limited circumstances where we believe in good faith that disclosure is required under the law. For example, we may be required to disclose personal information to cooperate with regulators or law enforcement authorities, to comply with a legal process such as court order, subpoena, search warrant, or law enforcement request. 

**Cookies  
** We use a variety of technologies on our sites. Among these are cookies; files that Web browsers place on a computer’s hard drive and are used to tell us whether customers and visitors have visited the Site previously. 

Cookies do not identify you personally. They merely recognize your browser. 

We also keep track of activity on our website via log files stored on our web servers. We collect information such as IP address, browser type and version, and pages you view. We also keep track of how you got to our site and any links you click on to leave our site. Once you leave our site, we do not track you. We use your website activity to assist us in offering you a personalized Web experience, assist you with technical support, diagnose problems with our server, administer our websites and to tailor our product and service offerings to you and our customers. 

**Security  
** We take every precaution to protect the confidentiality and security of your personal information. ScoutLander provides unique user names and passwords that must be entered each time a user logs on. These safeguards help prevent unauthorized access to data store on our servers. 

**Choice/Opt-out  
** ScoutLander provides user the opportunity to opt-in, opt-out or change preferences via a link in the footer of most email messages. These options are made available when you sign-up for a trial or subscription account. Alternatively, you may email us at support@ScoutLander.com. 

Some communications are necessary for ScoutLander customers (e.g. important account and billing notifications). You must cancel your ScoutLander account to unsubscribe from these communications. To cancel your ScoutLander account, please email us at support@ScoutLander.com. 

**Notification of Changes  
** If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on the ScoutLander Website. So our users are always aware of what information we collect, how it is used, and under what circumstances, if any, then we disclose it.
